I am a software engineer with 2-3 years of professional experience. I primarily use JavaScript and Python to accomplish amazing things through programming. Lately I have become passionate about backend development, and it has been my primary focus when it comes to learning new technologies.

Employment

Configuration Analyst

Forward Insurance

Nov. 2021 - Present

- Strong development skills and software fundamentals when building insurance-based applications
- Experience working with large native code bases with significant complexity
- Collaborated and worked with teams of experienced developers in a team environment to build insurance-based applications using best practices
- Developed, tested, shipped and supported products used by thousands of users daily

Independent Software Developer

Forward Insurance

June 2021 - Present

Grad Date: May 2016

Nov. 2023 - Present

- Designed and build simple, tasteful websites, brand portfolios, and mockup websites for clients
- Built structured web applications for both mobile and desktop devices
- Worked to build and update websites through various third-party website building services
- Design and built front-end web applications from concept to completion

Skills

• Languages: Python, JavaScript

Technologies: React, Vue, Git, Shells and Terminal, CSS, HTML

Other: Figma, Photoshop

Education

Niagara College: Electrical (Trades) Boot.dev: Backend Development